Spark supports both random splits and k-fold cross-validation.
Spark 支持 randomSplit 和 k-fold cross-validation 两种验证方式
Let's just start with general splits.
让我们先看一下 randomSplit
With the method name exactly the same,
与方法名称完全相同
we can break the data frame into two parts.
我们可以将 dataframe 分为两部分
So, for example in this case,
在这种情况下
it depends until the data goes to train and 20 percent to test.
80% 的数据用于训练 20％的数据用于测试
If we want to create really friends subsets for training, testing,
如果我们想创建三个子数据集用于训练  测试
and validation, we can just call this method again on the second part.
和验证 我们可以用两次这个方法
So, we could do something like this.
我们可以做这么做
First, break the dataset into train with 60 percent
首先 将数据集的 60％  用于训练
of the data and then the rest gets 40 percent,
然后剩下的 40％ 进行第二次拆分
and then split the rest 50-50 percent to test and validation.
将剩下的数据五五分成测试和验证
This way, the train set will have 60 percent of the original DataFrame,
这样 训练数据将拥有原始DataFrame的60％，
test and validation both 20-20 percent of the original data.
测试和验证各拥有 20％ 的原始数据
By fixing the randomSplit,
让随机种子不变
we can also make sure that the split is reproducible.
我们可以确保每次分割的数据是相同的
However, common these throughout and we are just use train and test,
我们把这两列给注释掉 只保留训练集和测试集
to train the logistic regression model we used before.
来训练之前用过的逻辑回归模型
So here is the pipeline we used in the previous video,
这是我们上一个视频中使用的管道
now we can train on the train set only.
现在我们只能在训练集上训练模型了
One similarly strain, we can just transform the test set.
模型训练好之后  我们可以对测试集进行变换
Since we did a random split,
由于我们做了 randomSplit
the first checkered is a different one than the one we are used to,
第一行记录的结果与我们之前看到的不同
but we certainly got the prediction here.
不过我们也会有预测结果
So let's see how well this model did on the training set.
那么让我们看看这个模型在训练集上的表现如何
So we have the correct label for
正确的标签
about 7,700 of the 20,000 records we have,
占了 20,000 条记录中的 7,700 条
I'll just save what that number is.
好了让我们看看准确率是多少
So our accuracy is around 30 percent,
我们的准确率大约是 30％
that's a lot worse than what we saw earlier.
这比之前的结果要糟糕得多
But at least now we have a more realistic idea about the accuracy of our model.
但至少现在我们对模型的准确性有一个更现实的看法
For k-fold cross-validation, we can use the cross-validation method.
对于k-fold cross-validation 我们可以使用 CrossValidator 这个方法
In the cross-validatior parameters,
在 CrossValidator 参数中
we can specify the estimator we would like to use,
我们可以指定想要使用的估算器
and that's going to be our pipeline from earlier.
这里写的是我们之前的管道
The parameter grid, if we want to do a quick search on
如果我们想针对参数组合使用网格搜索的话 这里就写 paramGrid
a setup parameter combinations, the evaluator,
Evaluator 参数
in our case that should be the multi-class classification evaluator,
我们这里就写多级分类评估器
as well as the number of faults of course.
还有这里的  numfolds 进行多少次交叉验证
In each fault, the one over num faults,
在每此验证中 1/numFolds 的数据
part of the data goes into testing,
会成为测试集
the rest is used for training.
其余的用于训练
So for example if we choose the value of three,
例如 如果我们写 3
then we will train our model on two-thirds of
那么三分之二的数据会变成训练集
the data and keep one third as a test set and repeat this process three times.
三分之一的数据作为测试集 并重复此过程三次
For the parameter grid,
对于 paramGrid 来说
we can try to experiment with the number of words we keep in our TF-IDF features.
我们用在 TF-IDF 中保留的单词数量
So let's try 10 and 20,000 words.
我们尝试一下 10000 和20000个单词
So, since it was three fold cross validation and we have these two parameters,
由于进行了三次交叉验证 同时我们有这两个参数
we will need to train six models into all.
所以我们一共需要训练六种模型
Okay let's see.
好的 让我们看看
Was there typos did I make?
写错了吗
Okay, training all these six models,
好的 训练这六个模型
we have taken a little bit longer.
会花一点时间
But let's just run this and wait.
运行它并等待
Once the training is done,
训练完成后
we can check the average performance of the parameter set.
我们看看这两个参数的平均效果
It seems that doubling the number of words only slightly improved the results,
似乎将单词数量加倍只能略微改善结果
so we have an accuracy just below
一个准确性
37 percent and a little bit over 37 percent.
略低于 37％ 另一个略高于 37％
We can also check the accuracy of the test set.
我们还可以看一下测试集的准确率
So in this particular case,
这个案例中
we see a slightly higher number of correct predictions than before.
正确预测数量比以前略高